JAN BRUS

FRONTEND DEVELOPER WITH FULL-STACK EXPERIENCES

I'm a software engineer from Czechia with broad range of experiences. I'm a professional since 2010 and also father of 4 girls.

I can speak: Czech (native C2) English (C1) Russian (A2)

CONTACT INFORMATION

- Životice u Nového Jičína 83, 74272, Czech Republic
- janbrus.inbox@gmail.com www.janbrus.cz
- in Linkedln: @janbrus

EDUCATION

Brno University of Technology

BACHELORS DEGREE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY (2010)

Wrote bachelors thesis on multiplatform game in java

Czech university of life sciences

MASTERS DEGREE IN SYSTEM ENGINEERING AND INFORMATICS (2018)

 Wrote master thesis on cash register software for small businesses



TECHNICAL EXPERIENCES

Development areas: Frontend (Angular, HTML/CSS/javascript), backend (java, C#), Windows applications, graphic design, databases, middleware **Languages/technologies:** Typescript, SQL, java, C# .Net **Tools:** VS Code, IDEA, GIT, Jira, Agile, Kanban, Photoshop

WORK EXPERIENCE

Angular developer

ZENTITY (2021-TODAY)

- Front-end development for a South African largest bank project. Web application for clients of the bank.
- Angular, Microfrontends, Jira, nx, ngrx, GIT

Full-stack developer

ON SEMICONDUCTOR/ONSEMI (2018-2021)

- Started in middleware team on a data transfer platform
- Switched to Angular development of a business application from scratch (as the only developer)
- Angular, java Spring backend, Postgre, GIT, Jira

Team leader / Senior application developer

IDC S.R.O. (2015 - 2018)

- Leads a team of 4 developers and 1 tester
- Working in a multi-team environment
- C# .Net WPF application development using Scrum methodology, JIRA, GIT, Entity Framework

Freelance and personal projects

(2015-TODAY)

- Mostly WordPress webs, graphic design, SEO
- OpenVidu streaming server
- JBTemplates (website with free templates, Stripe payment)
- 20+ graphic web designs